[{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664182116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":46475,"timeElapsed":190278},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":31587,"timeElapsed":221873},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":25490,"timeElapsed":247368},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664255377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":16166,"timeElapsed":263540},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":13227,"timeElapsed":276777},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":14268,"timeElapsed":291053},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9384,"timeElapsed":300445},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664298528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":6239,"timeElapsed":306691},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":8297,"timeElapsed":314996},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":20024,"timeElapsed":338004},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9130,"timeElapsed":347140},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":12397,"timeElapsed":359545},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9110,"timeElapsed":368660},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":8058,"timeElapsed":376722},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7152,"timeElapsed":383881},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5532,"timeElapsed":389418},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664387923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6663,"timeElapsed":396086},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664393258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5327,"timeElapsed":401421},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14596,"timeElapsed":418017},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":12431,"timeElapsed":430453},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":7247,"timeElapsed":437705},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":15830,"timeElapsed":453539},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8047,"timeElapsed":461592},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9050,"timeElapsed":470647},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664469706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7215,"timeElapsed":477869},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664480868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":11156,"timeElapsed":489031},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664489325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8452,"timeElapsed":497488},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664529576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":36564,"timeElapsed":537739},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664536551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6970,"timeElapsed":544714},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664547568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":11012,"timeElapsed":555731},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664556739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":9165,"timeElapsed":564902},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664561945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5199,"timeElapsed":570108},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4087,"timeElapsed":574201},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664571617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5575,"timeElapsed":579780},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664584571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":12951,"timeElapsed":592734},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664588913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4340,"timeElapsed":597076},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664604425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13817,"timeElapsed":612588},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664609409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4979,"timeElapsed":617572},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664618509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":626672},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664624606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6093,"timeElapsed":632769},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664630768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":6158,"timeElapsed":638931},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664633937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3164,"timeElapsed":642100},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664639625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5683,"timeElapsed":647788},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664644982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":5352,"timeElapsed":653145},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664651923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6936,"timeElapsed":660086},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664669319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":15656,"timeElapsed":677482},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664681428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":12104,"timeElapsed":689591},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664689815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":8381,"timeElapsed":697978},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664695223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5403,"timeElapsed":703386},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664700601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5373,"timeElapsed":708764},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664703932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3326,"timeElapsed":712095},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664709010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":5072,"timeElapsed":717173},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664730233,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":21217,"timeElapsed":738395},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664738778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8539,"timeElapsed":746941},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664747167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":8383,"timeElapsed":755330},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664769320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":19777,"timeElapsed":777483},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664774148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4821,"timeElapsed":782311},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664782582,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8428,"timeElapsed":790745},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664792806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10218,"timeElapsed":800969},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664797649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4838,"timeElapsed":805812},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664806830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9175,"timeElapsed":814993},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664809995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3159,"timeElapsed":818158},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664816791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":6790,"timeElapsed":824954},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664824162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7365,"timeElapsed":832325},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664832166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":7999,"timeElapsed":840329},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664852525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":17764,"timeElapsed":860687},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664861632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9102,"timeElapsed":869794},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664883495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":21858,"timeElapsed":891658},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664895674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":12174,"timeElapsed":903837},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664906242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10563,"timeElapsed":914405},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664913209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6962,"timeElapsed":921372},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664920320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7105,"timeElapsed":928482},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664925093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4768,"timeElapsed":933256},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664931071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5973,"timeElapsed":939234},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664953248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":20587,"timeElapsed":961411},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664959035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5781,"timeElapsed":967198},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664971760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12721,"timeElapsed":979923},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664980550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":8786,"timeElapsed":988712},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664995734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":15179,"timeElapsed":1003897},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665001972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":6233,"timeElapsed":1010135},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665011188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":9212,"timeElapsed":1019351},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665015763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4570,"timeElapsed":1023926},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5962,"timeElapsed":1029894},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665040147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13867,"timeElapsed":1048310},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665047088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6936,"timeElapsed":1055250},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665061974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":14881,"timeElapsed":1070136},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665075046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":13065,"timeElapsed":1083209},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665088147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":13095,"timeElapsed":1096310},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665094912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6759,"timeElapsed":1103074},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665102661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7744,"timeElapsed":1110823},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665111095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8428,"timeElapsed":1119257},{"subjectID":"n7afogjvmk","prolificID":"6709b4f01db5043c8e3472df","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742145bbe40180fbcd4a47","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665120049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8950,"timeElapsed":1128212}]